My first guest is a great actress
我的第一位嘉宾是位杰出的女演员
and you can see her as wonder woman in the new movie Wonder Woman 1984
她在新的电影《神奇女侠1984》中扮演神奇女侠
It’s in select theatres and IMAX on Christmas Day
电影会在圣诞节那天在精选剧院和IMAX上映
and will also be available on the same day on HBO Max
并且也将于当天在HBO Max上线
Here is Gal Gadot!
这是盖尔·加朵！
Gal! My goodness is so good to...
盖尔！啊这简直太好了…
We’re hugging you from here
我们从这里拥抱你
I’m hugging you from here, too
我也是
Oh, pal, it’s so great to see you
噢，见到你可真太高兴了，朋友
Thank you so much for coming back to our show
感谢你回到我们的节目
Can you believe Wonder Woman 1984 is finally here?
你敢相信《神奇女侠1984》终于要上映了？
It’s here, it’s finally happening
它就在这里，正在发生
I can and I can’t at the same time
我可以想象，但我不能同时和你一起见证这一切
We’ve been waiting for such a long time
我们已经等了太久
for to be able to share this with the world
终于可以和全世界分享它了
and now is the moment
现在这一刻到来了
And it’s so surreal that we’ve just releasing the movie
我们要发布电影了，这感觉太离谱了
and I don’t get to see you like everything is virtual
就像我现在没法看到真实的你，一切都是虚拟的
The world had gone crazy
这个世界太疯狂了
I know, but it’s a great...
我明白，但是这很棒…
And I’m supper excited
我现在非常兴奋
I want to say that this movie has more action than the first one
我想说这部电影比起第一部电影多了更多的战斗
Did you know that going into it that you’re gonna be like
你知道当你扮演这个角色的时候会像
I’m going to be exhausted in this one?
我要为此精疲力尽这样？
Yes, I did. Patty made a big point about
是的，的确如此。帕蒂提到了一个重要的问题
wanting to have minimum account of CGI
是关于想要最少的CGI（电脑三维动画）
which is great and I love this idea
这很棒，我很支持这样做
I just didn’t really understood what it meant for me
我只是没有真正明白这对我意味着什么
and what it did mean was that we just, you know
它的意思是我们只能，你知道的
both Kristen, too, and I had to do so much
克里斯汀和我都必须做很多事情
So much stunt work by ourselves
需要我们自己做很多特技
I want to show you one thing that I noticed when I watched it
我想给你看一个东西，这是我在观看的时候注意到的
There was one kick that you did that I want to say...
我要说的是你踢过的一脚…
Oh that
哦这可真是
your body was like, you were parallel, like it was…
你的身体就像是，你是完全平行的
The front kick, the front kick lay out
一个前踢，前面的脚踢出来了
The front kick lay out is what it’s called?
所谓的前踢是指？
It’s horizontal and…
这是水平的…
Were you on wires?
你在威亚上吗？
That was assisted majorly
那主要是协助我的
and that was also my stunt girl who’s like, amazing
那也是我的特技动作，真的太神奇了
I wanted, cause I asked the studio for this clip
我问演播室要了这个剪辑片段
cause I just wanted to watch it
因为我只是想要看它
Do you mind if I watch this clip?
你介意我看这个前踢吗？
Dave, could we watch this? - Sure
戴夫，我们可以看一下吗？-当然
Yeah, let’s watch it
好，让我们来看一下
Look at this! Stop right here!
看这个动作！停，就这儿！
Look at that! Look at that! Perfection!
看那个！看那个! 完美！
That is unbelievable!
这太难以置信了
And holding the gun and the lasso
同时还拿着枪和套索
And the lasso. I mean, look at that.
还有套索。我的意思是，看看那个
That’s the poster right there. Come on.
这一刻就像海报一样。来吧
I also remember seeing something
我记得好像看到过什么
I thought it was you flying in the invisible jet or something
我记得是你坐隐形喷气式飞机或其他什么东西飞翔
I thought it was a spoiler or something
好像是流出的剧透照片
cause it looked like you were sitting in the street
因为看起来你好像坐在大街上
I know, I know
我知道的我明白
That was not the invisible jet, that was me being a major pain
那不是隐形的喷气机，那让我感到非常痛苦
We shut down Penn Avenue in Washington D.C.
我们封锁了华盛顿特区的宾夕法尼亚大道
for a few days and I had to do like this intense running
几天了，我不得不像这样如此激烈的奔跑
and I was wired, like from here and from here
我被威亚固定了，从这里到这里
and they pulled me as the same speed as Usain Bolt
他们拉我让我以与博尔特比赛获胜时相同的速度奔跑
ran when he won one of his medals
当他赢得他的勋章之一的时候
He’s the fastest man in the world
他是全世界跑得最快的男人
Yeah, I know. So we had to, so that’s what we did
是的，我知道。因此我们不得不，这就是我们所做的
Oh, so you needed to
噢，因此你需要
cause you’re actually running, and the wires are pulling you
所以当威亚拉你的时候你实际上正在跑步
But the craziest thing is you gonna make sure that like every time, every stride
但最疯狂的是你必须确保每一步
you hit the floor so it does look like you’re running
你都踩到地上，所以他看起来就像你真的在跑步一样
Yeah, I auditioned, and yeah, they actually didn’t even call me back at all,
是的，我也试镜了，是的，我没…他们甚至没打电话给我
but whatever, it’s a little rude, but...
但无所谓了，好像有点粗鲁，但…
I will say our pal Kristen Wiig crushes it in this movie
我会说我们的朋友克里斯汀•威格在这部电影里征服了它
She’s also in the movie
她也在这部电影里
We actually adore each other so much
实际上我们非常敬佩彼此
We had a crazy instant connection, it was like
我们有一个非常疯狂的密切的联系，这就像她
She, because the movie was so laborious and they were so
因为电影的拍摄是如此的艰苦，他们是如此的
It was very long and we shot the movie for eight months
这太久了，这部电影我们拍了八个月
in five different locations, and it was just, like super physical as well
在五个不同的地方，这就像，生理上的亲密
The fact that she was there with me doing these crazy things
她和我一起做这些疯狂的事
but also, like, being her, she’s like the most
但是，作为她，她最喜欢…
She's so, you know, but she’s like I’ll tell everyone else
你知道，但她就像，我会告诉其他所有人
Guys you’re missing on not knowing Kristen Wiig,
那些不了解克里斯汀·威格的人，你们都错过了
She’s like fun and funny, and open, like, she made this experience
她有趣，搞笑，开明，她让我有这样的经历
so, so delightful for me, and I’m super grateful
所以，我很高兴，我非常感激
We know that you guys became fast friends and really good friends on the set
我们知道你们在片场上很快成为了好朋友
and this is really very very cool
这真的很酷
You guys sent us one of your music videos
你们给我们发了一个音乐录影带
You made a music video together, it’s very low budget
你们一起拍了一段音乐视频，据说这视频的制作成本很低
Here is an exclusive world premiere of Gal Gadot and Kristen Wiig’s video.
这是盖尔·加朵和克里斯汀·威格视频的独家世界首映
Take a look.
来让我们看看
♪ Gal and Kristen having fun! ♪
盖尔和克里斯汀，很开心！
♪ We are Gal and Kristen and we're having fun ♪
我们是盖尔和克里斯汀，我们很开心
♪ Sometimes we run, jump in the air ♪
有时我们跑，在空中跳跃
♪ Sometimes we stare and then flip our hair ♪
有时我们盯着看，然后撩起我们的头发
♪ We’re friends, and we like science ♪
我们是朋友，我们喜欢科学
♪ We feel comfortable in total silence ♪
我们在安静的时刻感到舒服
♪ Come on everybody, dancing in the sun ♪
拜托，各位，在阳光下跳舞
♪ Cause we’re Gal and Krissy ♪
因为我们是盖尔和克丽丝
♪ And we’re having fun! ♪
我们很开心！
I love you
我爱你
我们喜欢对方，对吗？
结束
It’s a fake applause at the end, and the kids
最后是虚拟的掌声，和孩子们
It is honestly
老实说
Oh, my God
哦，天啊
And we are having fun!
我们很开心！
Gal and Krissy, and we are having fun!
盖尔和克里斯，我们很开心！
Dude, that’s catchy
伙计，这很吸引人
The claps and everything
拍手和这一切
That was the funniest thing
这真的是最有趣的事
Can you tell everyone what’s going on in Wonder Woman 1984?
你能告诉大家《神奇女侠1984》里都发生了什么吗？
Oh, my God. Wow, where do I begin without giving away too many spoilers?
哦，天哪。 哇，我从哪里开始不会给太多的剧透？
What I can tell you is
我能告诉你的是
it’s the most ambitious movie I’ve ever got to make
这是我拍过的最雄心勃勃的电影
As far as the story telling we have four different storylines
就故事情节而言，我们有四条不同的故事线
As far as the action goes, like we talked about
就战斗而言，就像我们之前谈到的
There’s so much action for real
里面有很多真实的战斗
As for as location and the scope, it’s huge
至于地点和范围，它是庞大的
And I’m very, very excited to share it with everybody
我非常，非常兴奋能和大家分享这一切
And I hope that people are going to enjoy it
我希望人们会喜欢这部电影
and have a wonderful two and a half hours watching it
这将会是精彩的两个半小时
We need it right now more than ever
我们现在比以前更需要它
I want to show everyone a clip from the film
我想给大家看一段电影剪辑的片段
Here is Gal Gadot in Wonder Woman 1984, Take a look
这里是盖尔加朵在《神奇女侠1984》，来看看吧
Well, aren’t you resourceful?
好吧，你不是足智多谋的吗？
Come with me
跟我来
No, I don’t think so
不，我不这么认为
Remove this woman, please. Permanently.
让这个女人消失，永远的
Are you OK?
你还好吗？
I don’t know
我不知道
Wonder Woman 1984 will be in select theaters and IMAX on Christmas Day
《神奇女侠1984》将在圣诞节上映
and will be available the same day on HBO max
并将在同一天在HBOmax上线